迈克 · 诺斯: 那么接下来我要做的就是获得
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So
the next thing am gonna do is obtain
类型检查器的引用。
a reference to the type checker.
类型检查器，它是编译的一部分,
The type checker,
which is part of the compile,
它需要你创建的所有类型和接口。
it is what takes all of the types and
the interface you create.
代码在内存中的表示抽象语法树,
And the abstract syntax tree which is
the in memory representation of your code,
对吧？
right?
所有的函数，参数，所有的东西
All of the functions and
the arguments and everything and
它将它们绑定在一起，并识别实际输入的支票。
it binds them together and identifies
what is going to actually typed check.
什么会起作用？
What is going to work?
确保所有内容都是等效的类型。
Make sure everything is type equivalent.
所以我们要用它来获取很多信息
So it's gonna be the source of a lot of
the information that we're gonna use to
注销文件。
log out documentation.
我们只需要把它记录到控制台上，让事情变得简单明了。
We're just gonna log it to the console
to keep things nice and simple.
接下来，我们将使用类型检查器来获取 TypeScript 符号和
Next, we'll use the type checker to
obtain the TypeScript symbol and
这个符号可以输入或输出。
the symbol is something that
can be imported or exported.
有名字的东西记住一个符号有三个插槽,
It's something with a name,
remember you have three slots on a symbol,
值、类型和名称空间，这就是我们在这里要处理的。
value, type, and namespace,
that's what we are working with here.
每个文件都与一个文件相关联。
And each file is associated with one.
因此，我们将获取所有文件，对它们进行迭代，然后
So we are going to take all of our files,
iterate over them, and
对于每个文件，我们都会询问这个符号,
for each file,
we're going to ask the symbol, sorry,
向检查人员要文件所在位置的符号。
ask the checker for
the symbol at the location of that file.
这就是你得到的,
This is just the way you get,
我们有效地使用了一点语言服务器。
we're effectively using the language
server a little bit here.
我们说，我们询问检查人员说，这里有一个位置。
We're saying, we're querying
the checker saying, here's a location.
它基本上是文件中的字符零。
It is character zero in the file,
basically.
告诉我那里的工具提示符号是什么？
Give me whatever the tool tip would
be there, like what is the symbol?
然后我们过滤掉所有未定义的信息。
And then we're filtering out
anything that might be undefined.
如果有某种编译错误，或者
If there was a compile error of some sort,
or something was really wrong with one of
在我们的声明文件中，有些文件可能与符号无关。
our declaration files, some files might
not be associated with the symbol.
如果他们不能成功输入检查，而我们有了打字稿
If they couldn't successfully type
check and we had our TypeScript
设置真的很松散，其中一些可能会回来像,
settings really relaxed,
some of these might come back like,
我不能给你任何东西，它就这么消失了。
I can't give you anything for
this, it's just gone.
迈克 · 诺斯: 现在我们有了符号，迈克 · 诺斯: 我只是
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So now we have symbols,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: And I'm just
我们要取消注释这块这里，我们只是有点走过它的一步一步。
gonna uncomment this block here and we'll
just kinda walk through it's step by step.
迈克 · 诺斯: 实际上，让我们逐步地尝试一下。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Actually,
let's try it out incrementally.
所以我要注销每个符号的名称。
So I'm just going to
logout each symbols name.
我们从那里开始，这是一个好的开始。
We'll start there, that's a good start.
迈克 · 诺斯: 好的，这给我们提供了和以前基本相同的东西。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Okay, so this is giving
us basically the same thing as before.
让我只是确保我的另一个控制台日志消失了，它是。
Let me just make sure my other
console log is gone, and it is.
所以这里一定产生了这个输出。
So this must be producing
this output down here.
一个与文件相关的符号，它的名字，将成为该文件的一部分。
A symbol associated with a file,
it's name, is gonna be part of that file.
因此，如果文件有导出，我们将在这里输入这个分支。
So if the file has exports,
we will enter this branch here.
所以让我们试着编译并运行它。
So let's try to compile that and run it.
迈克诺斯: 我们只是，符号有一个属性叫做出口，和
&gt;&gt; Mike North: And we're just,
symbol has a property called exports, and
我只是把它从标志上拿下来。
I'm just grabbing that
right off of the symbol.
看起来它确实有导出，所以让我们遍历导出。
Looks like it does have exports,
so let's iterate over the exports.
他们的类型恰好是一个叫做 UnderscoreEscapeMap 的东西，它是一个字典。
Their type happens to be something called
an UnderscoreEscapeMap, it's a dictionary.
迈克 · 诺斯: 抱歉一直在滚动,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Sorry for
all the scrolling,
我只是想一点一点地揭开这个秘密这样我们就可以一起跟进了。
it's just I wanna reveal this bit
by bit so we can all follow along.
所以我们要在导出上进行迭代。
So we're gonna iterate over the export.
对于每个导出，我们要注销它的名称和
And for each export,
we're gonna log out its name and
在类型检查器中使用此技术获取其类型。
use this technique with a type
checker to obtain its type.
这和我们用来获取每个文件符号的东西完全一样,
This is the exact same thing we
used to get each file's symbol,
1. getsymbolicatlocation，getTypeAtLocation.
getSymbolAtLocation, getTypeAtLocation.
这将给我们一个类型，然后这是 typeToString，不言自明。
So this will give us a type, and then
this is typeToString, self-explanatory.
让我们看看这是什么样子。
Let's see what this looks like.
迈克 · 诺斯: 找到了，就是这个符号的名字。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Here we go, there's the
name of the symbol that's this right here.
然后打印出这个字符串,
And then this prints out this string,
看起来很像我们在工具提示中看到的。
which looks a lot like what
we're seeing in our tool tips.
这里有几个步骤,
Now, there are couple steps involved here,
但实际上一旦我们创建了程序掌握了文件,
but really, once we create our program,
get ahold of a file,
我们可以开始利用它所有的出口
we can start accessing all its exports and
找出哪一个是函数，并开始检查它们的参数。
figure out which one are functions and
start checking on their arguments.
在今天的某个时候，我有一个关于 JSDoc 标签的问题。
At some point today,
I got a question about JSDoc tags.
我想是你问的，蔡斯，你想知道这是什么的一部分
I think you asked it, Chase,
where you wondered is this part of what
打字稿是在解析，还是 VS 代码只是把它添加到工具类型中？
the TypeScript is parsing or is it
VS Code just adding it to a tool type?
事实证明，TypeScript 理解这些 JSDoc 标签，所以下面是我们的值。
It turns out TypeScript understand
these JSDoc tags, so here's our value.
它有一个叫做 getjsDocTags 的方法，剩下的就是
It's got a method called getjsDocTags and
the rest of this is just getting
我们可以很容易地在控制台上看到它,
it into a form where we can
easily see it in the console,
迈克 · 诺斯: 好了。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: And there we go.
所以这些符合代码中的注释。
So these correspond to
the comments in that code.
让我打开代码就这样
Let me open up the code just so
我们可以比较登记出去的数据，这就对了。
we can compare what's being logged out,
there you go.
还有另一种方法，比如属性，我们可以在这里看到这个字符串。
There's another way, like property we
could access to see this string up here.
但这看起来很像我们在底部注销的东西。
But this looks a lot like what
we're logging out on the bottom.
所以，如果你有兴趣检查你的代码，以确保没有人的
So if you were interested in checking
your code to make sure that nobody's
访问某个库的旧版本，或者如果你想确保
accessing this old version of some library
or if you wanted to make sure that
没有人的，你想建立一个自定义的规则之类的,
nobody's, you wanted to build
a custom linting rule of some sort,
你需要了解这些代码是如何组合在一起的。
where you need to understand how all
of this code is assembled together.
是一个很好的工具，因为它可以理解 JavaScript 和 JavaScript
TypeScript is a great tool for that,
because it understands JavaScript and
打字稿也同样出色。
TypeScript equally well.
你可以得到这些非常合理的数据结构
And you get these pretty reasonable
data structures out that
你可以遍历并爬过它，然后用它来做这样的事情。
you can iterate over and crawl through and
use it for something like this.